http://georgiasports.blogspot.com/2008/08/privacy-policy-statement.html

Georgia Sports Blog FanShop
Nike Georgia Bulldogs Youth Red Sideline Core Football T-ShirtPrice: $21.99Georgia Nike Sideline AeroBill Coaches Performance Adjustable HatPrice: $29.99Georgia Bulldogs Women's Sideline ClutchPrice: $84.99Georgia Bulldogs Nike Elite Coaches Sideline Dri-FIT Polo - BlackPrice: $84.99Georgia Nike 2018 Coaches Sideline Performance Long Sleeve WhitePrice: $49.99
August 6, 2008
Privacy Policy Statement
Site Name: Georgia Sports BlogPublisher:
Paul W.Email:
decaturdawg at hotmail (dot) comPolicy Updated:
August. 7, 2009The Georgia Sports is published by me (Paul W.), and it operates using software developed by Blogger.com (a Google product). Google tracks your username and password for commenting. As the the site's publisher, I have no ability to view that information.For each visitor to our Web page, our traffic monitoring site automatically recognizes the visitor's domain name, but not the e-mail address. We collect aggregate information on what pages visitors view for the last 100 visitors. The information we collect is used to evaluate aggregate traffic patterns such a visits per hour, day, week or month.With respect to Ad Servers:To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we sometimes have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. In the past, we have partnered with Google and Amazon for these types of services.With Respect to Advertisers:Our advertisers may request personally identifiable information from you at the point of purchase, we suggest you read their privacy policy before doing so.With Respect to Future Changes:From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice.
If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes.No Warranties or Guarantees:While this privacy policy states standards, and while
efforts will be made to meet the said standards, the site editor is not in a
position to guarantee compliance with these standards. There may be factors
beyond the site editor's control that may result in disclosure of data. Consequently,
the site editor offers no warranties or representations as regards maintenance
or non-disclosure of data.If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact or Email us at the info above.Paul W.
Tweet
Posted by
Unknown
at
Wednesday, August 06, 2008
Labels:
Admin
0
comments:
Post a Comment
Newer Post
Older Post
Home
Football Resources
* TV Schedule (All)
CFB By the Numbers
CFB Historical Scores
CFB Stats
Football Data Warehouse
Football Outsiders
Football Study Hall
Football Toolbox
NCAA Financial Reports
NYC Dawgs
NYC Dawgs (Facebook)
Nashville Bulldogs
Quad Cities (Illinois/Iowa)
Tampa Bay Bulldogs
Ten-O Gym Dog Club
UGA Tip Off Club
Upstate SC Dawgs
Valdosta Dawgs
Women's TipOff Club
Young Alumni Program
Disclaimer
Georgia Sports Blog is an independent site. It is not associated with the University of Georgia, the UGA Athletic Department or any other official entity.
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
UGA Football Tickets
UGA Football Tickets
Georgia Football Tix
UGA 45 Austin Peay 0UGA 41 South Carolina 17UGA 49 MTSU 7UGA 43 Mizzou 29UGA 38 Tenn 12UGA 41 Vandy 13LSU 36 UGA 13UGA 36 UF 17UGA 34 UK 17UGA 27 AU 10UGA 66 UMass 27UGA 45 Tech 21SEC Championship:UA 35 UGA 28Sugar Bowl Tix
Follow me on Twitter
TylerDawgden
Blog Archive
Blog Archive
October 2018 (2)
September 2018 (1)
August 2018 (1)
July 2018 (1)
June 2018 (2)
May 2018 (2)
April 2018 (1)
March 2018 (5)
February 2018 (1)
January 2018 (10)
December 2017 (19)
November 2017 (11)
October 2017 (13)
September 2017 (16)
August 2017 (12)
July 2017 (5)
June 2017 (6)
May 2017 (5)
March 2017 (4)
February 2017 (5)
January 2017 (8)
December 2016 (4)
November 2016 (20)
October 2016 (22)
September 2016 (22)
August 2016 (17)
July 2016 (6)
June 2016 (7)
May 2016 (5)
April 2016 (7)
March 2016 (18)
February 2016 (5)
January 2016 (20)
December 2015 (20)
November 2015 (44)
October 2015 (42)
September 2015 (74)
August 2015 (48)
July 2015 (17)
June 2015 (11)
May 2015 (4)
April 2015 (7)
March 2015 (17)
February 2015 (11)
January 2015 (5)
December 2014 (43)
November 2014 (87)
October 2014 (76)
September 2014 (96)
August 2014 (101)
July 2014 (63)
June 2014 (41)
May 2014 (9)
April 2014 (22)
March 2014 (12)
February 2014 (32)
January 2014 (55)
December 2013 (41)
November 2013 (59)
October 2013 (84)
September 2013 (128)
August 2013 (107)
July 2013 (58)
June 2013 (40)
May 2013 (25)
April 2013 (36)
March 2013 (44)
February 2013 (63)
January 2013 (70)
December 2012 (56)
November 2012 (90)
October 2012 (79)
September 2012 (87)
August 2012 (58)
July 2012 (56)
June 2012 (22)
May 2012 (6)
April 2012 (6)
March 2012 (27)
February 2012 (30)
January 2012 (38)
December 2011 (27)
November 2011 (86)
October 2011 (45)
September 2011 (84)
August 2011 (67)
July 2011 (38)
June 2011 (30)
May 2011 (6)
April 2011 (2)
March 2011 (19)
February 2011 (1)
January 2011 (7)
December 2010 (5)
November 2010 (11)
October 2010 (23)
September 2010 (39)
August 2010 (9)
July 2010 (12)
June 2010 (20)
May 2010 (14)
April 2010 (11)
March 2010 (38)
February 2010 (25)
January 2010 (50)
December 2009 (41)
November 2009 (54)
October 2009 (47)
September 2009 (70)
August 2009 (52)
July 2009 (42)
June 2009 (41)
May 2009 (52)
April 2009 (44)
March 2009 (49)
February 2009 (51)
January 2009 (63)
December 2008 (73)
November 2008 (64)
October 2008 (111)
September 2008 (119)
August 2008 (139)
July 2008 (95)
June 2008 (71)
May 2008 (64)
April 2008 (67)
March 2008 (67)
February 2008 (44)
January 2008 (41)
December 2007 (76)
November 2007 (99)
October 2007 (72)
September 2007 (69)
August 2007 (80)
July 2007 (41)
June 2007 (72)
May 2007 (45)
April 2007 (59)
March 2007 (54)
February 2007 (87)
January 2007 (101)
December 2006 (94)
November 2006 (89)
October 2006 (83)
September 2006 (100)
August 2006 (111)
July 2006 (83)
June 2006 (73)
May 2006 (82)
April 2006 (75)
March 2006 (87)
February 2006 (81)
January 2006 (70)
December 2005 (74)
November 2005 (77)
October 2005 (59)
September 2005 (76)
August 2005 (41)
July 2005 (35)
June 2005 (7)
May 2005 (6)
April 2005 (9)
March 2005 (1)
February 2005 (1)
January 2005 (2)
December 2004 (2)
November 2004 (2)
October 2004 (2)
September 2004 (1)
August 2004 (2)
December 2003 (1)
Top UGA Blogs & Sites
* DawgBone
* DawgSports.com
* Get the Picture
* Marc Weiszer (ABH)
* Seth Emerson (GA Bulldog Blog)
Passer's Remorse (bball)
UGA Hoops (DaugMan)
Copyright 2009 Georgia Sports Blog. Powered by Blogger
Blogger Templates create by Deluxe Templates. WP by Masterplan
